[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "It must be a rather surreal atmosphere, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "It's absolutely surreal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "JJS", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "What can you tell me about both those things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "I wish I could tell you more about how the police evicted protesters from here, but I can't, because our cameras and most journalists' cameras were not allowed in here for hours and hours.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Has it galvanized them to, perhaps, be even more protesting down there in bigger numbers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", ",", "RB", ",", "VB", "RB", "RBR", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "I think that's an outstanding question to be absolutely fair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "John Timoney, what is your reaction to what's been going on in this park for the last 24 hours?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Well, it was predictable that, eventually, this would come to a head.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 24"], "PERSON": ["John Timoney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1951"]}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "When were you at Penn State?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "I was there in 1951.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Penn State"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Have you spoken to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "I have not spoken to him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "What would you say if you got the chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "I'd just say I pray that the Lord will bless you and the Lord will keep you and the Lord will bless all of those people that are around you and help you all stand strong and learn that God does forgive wrong things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "When you first got wind of this, did you ever imagine it would become as big as this become?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "I think it was as big a shock to us in one sense as it has been to everyone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "You know, when you are asked, are you sexually attracted to young boys and it takes you 17 seconds to answer, you're basically hanging yourself, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Well, you know what was startling about watching that, I had the exact same reaction, Piers, to that moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"], "PERSON": ["Sara Gannon"]}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "How much did that come into play and preventing people who were, otherwise, apparently, good people like Joe Paterno from going to the police about these terrible crimes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Well, our reporter, Sara Gannon (ph), did a story last Friday.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Paterno"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Mickey, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Five-year break.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "I've always wondered, why would you -- in the middle of this dazzling film career, want to go and get beaten around the head?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "The acting wasn't something I was having fun doing anymore or liked doing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "You've always loved boxing, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "How did it go, the boxing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "It went good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "MD", "VB", ",", "MD", "VB", ",", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Did you ever think you could have been a proper contestant?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "I never say could have, would have, should have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "But what does it give you, that feeling when you get into the ring?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "You know what it was, I needed the discipline.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "And boy, was it the comeback movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Well, you know, I did the movie at a time when I still wasn't very bankable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "The guy did a really great job with the nose.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Is that from the fighting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "You know, I always had trouble with wrapping my hands, because my hands would swell up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Did you imagine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "I imagine it's hellish.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Why do you think you did it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Well, I did it because I had some issues when I was very young with authority and with physical --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "In the wilderness years, when you were walking, say, into a store in Hollywood, a grocery store or something, what was the reality of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "It was terrible.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "You actually hear that line?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Oh, yeah, didn't you used to be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "What was the worst name?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "I'm not going to go there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stallone"]}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Who were the guys, the other actors who really stuck by you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Well, Stallone helped me out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Had you seen each other since?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Once.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "When you met up again this time, how did it go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "It's always nerve-racking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "So when she first saw you again this time, was it affectionate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Well, the first time we saw each in over 20 years was last year or something.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Are you proud of it, from an acting point of view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "I have never been until in the last couple of years, kind of acknowledged it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "What was your view of the book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "I don't have any desire to read it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Anyway, what's the next thing you want to talk about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "No, but I -- I mean, it's fascinating.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Do you ever wonder about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "No, I don't have to wonder.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Mickey"]}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "You feel me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "I think I'm feeling you, Mickey.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "Do you understand them better?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "No, they're stronger than us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Are an easier guy to go out with, to date, to be with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", ",", "TO", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "No, I'm -- not necessarily, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Is that the ultimate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Listen, when I -- listen, just to get the second chance, they're letting me back in the door.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "Do you still feel that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Do you still drink much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "It wasn't the drinking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "ORGAN: What was your problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "My anger.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "And does that still flare up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Should I be feeling a little nervous here, Mickey?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "I would do it in a diplomatic way, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Mickey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "Does he know he butchered my mother?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "Now that he has seen your face, he knows.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "He came out to your premier last week?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Yes, he did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "Who told you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "You told me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "What do you make of what's happening with your country right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "I have -- I like the way you say with your country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "CD", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "What is going wrong with America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "I don't really have one, to be honest with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "Are you learning a bit of diplomatic tact in your old age, Mickey?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Mickey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "Do you think actors should spout off about politics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "I'll let you read my mind.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "There's a wild rumor you got engaged recently?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "No, I didn't get engaged.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "Are you with anyone in any serious way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "None of your business, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]